Guide to the Pittsburgh & Lake Erie Railroad Company Records, 1860-1999 AIS.1982.23
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Pittsburgh & Lake Erie Railroad, 1860-1999; VII.
  - Labor, 1850-1994; 4.
    - Telephone directory, Police Officer Instruction files (duties, training material), Accident Prevention training material, 1930-1960 (Box 150)
    - Crew assignments sheets, accident reports (1989-92), personal Injury reports (1989-92), Brake Information / Training, Pink Sheets (May 1982 - July 82), mechanical division annual reports and Pink Sheets, 1980-1990s (Box 151)
    - Instruction Files - Handling Messages, Bonner Cards, Tender Notices, Crew Callers, Crew Dispatchers, etc., 1970s (Box 152)
    - Yardmaster sick time, Master list regular and extra employees, extension on activity report, labor representatives, request for verification of employment, wage stabilization agreement, 1980s (Box 153)
    - Janitors Instructions and Correspondence, messengers handling mail, YS&T Yard Movement Card Bills, Ore Report, End of Month Report, Company fuel cars - heavy repair cars, Company coal, sand, and oil, 1970s (Box 154)
    - Time book, Chief Clerk Duties, Mediation Agreements Shop Crafts, Vacations Car Dept., Loco Diesel Shop, engineer and reserve engineer sheets, 1980s (Box 159)
    - Time claims or Grievances, 1970s (Box 164)
    - Time Claims or Grievances (6476 thru 6672 - Time Claims or Grievances, 6628 thru 6639 - 1st Div. NRAB see file E502, 6640 thru 6641 - Time claims or Grievances, 6642 - See Board File A3T2, 6643 thru 6646 - Time Claims or Grievances, 6647 - 1st Div. NRAB et al, 6648 thru 6652 - Time Claims or Grievances, 6653 - 1st Div. NRAB, 6654 thru 6675 - Time Claims or Grievances, 1950s (Box 165)
    - Time claims or Grievances (18876 - 2nd Div. NRAB see A15 V117, 18877 thru 19025), 1957-1960s (Box 166-168)
    - Agreement between P&LE and Yardmasters, Labor Agreements Effective 4/1/91, Mediation Agreements (UTU, BLE,ATDA,RYA,TCU & Telegraphers, Allied Services), P&LE Union Agreements, 1990s (Box 170)
    - Time Claims Clerks, Clerical Rosters, Bonding Service Clerks, Vacation Clerks, Office Machines, Taxi Cabs charges, Payroll Information Clerks, Wages working conditions advertisement district, clerks agreements holidays vacations wages etc, Grievances of Employers, etc., 1980s (Box 173)
    - Personal injuries starting January 1966, 1966-1977 (Box 174)
    - 3rd Division Awards (NRAB), A12E16A1, A14B4, A14B5, A14B6, A171, A172, 1950s (Box 178)
    - 2nd Division Awards (NRAB), A15V114 thru A15V118, 1960s (Box 179)
    - 3rd Division Awards (NRAB), 1960s (Box 180)
    - 2nd Division Awards (NRAB) A15V70 thru A15V91, 1980s (Box 182)
    - Employee Records Cards, 1870s-1950 (Box 183-185)
    - 11551 thru 11599 (Time Claims or Grievances), 11600 (2nd Div NRAB A15V22), 11601 to 11602 (Time Claims or Grievances), 11603 (2nd Div NRAB A15V25), 11604 thru 11718 (Time Claims or Grievances), 11719 thru 11725 (Time Claims or Grievances), 1960s (Box 186)
    - Matters of employees including five day work week, union shop agreements, vacations, requisitions, sight & hearing exams, insurance, sick time, etc.; files on Conrail, trackage rights, right of way, 1970s-1980s (Box 187)
    - Employee Records Files, includes some who participated in National Defense Program, 1960s-1980s (Box 188)
    - 3rd Division Awards A17-3 through A17-8, 1970s (Box 189)
    - Discipline of Employees Instructions; P&LE General Instructions; TWU Working Agreements and Public Law Board Cases; Monthly Safety Meetings; Brotherhood of Railway, Airline and Steamship Clerks; Leave of Absence, 1928-1990 (Box 190)
    - Employee Records Files, 1960s-1980s (Box 191)
    - Mechanical Department - Personal Injury Record Cards, Car and Locomotive, 1943-1974 (Box 260)
    - Index cards of employee's information, 1969-1983 (Box 289)
    - Transportation Department out of service prior to 1950, Wia to Zoll; eng contracts-cards, 1870s-1950 (Box 301)
    - Transportation Department employees out of service prior to 1950, Rei to Sow, 1870s-1950 (Box 302a-302b)
    - Transportation Department employees out of service prior to 1950, McD to Rei, 1870s-1950 (Box 303a-303b)
    - Transportation Department 50-80-20 out of service employees prior to 1950, Ge to Hr, 1870s-1950 (Box 304a-304b)
    - Transportation Department 80-50-20 out of service employees prior to 1950, Bu to Day, 1870s-1950 (Box 305a-305b)
    - Transportation Department 50-80-20 out of service employees prior to 1950, A to Brz, 1870s-1950 (Box 306a-306b)
    - Out of service employees, Stores Department, Ke to Miller, 1870s-1950 (Box 307)
    - Out of service storehouse department employees - Aa to Cloh, 1870s-1950 (Box 308)
    - Out of service employees, Stores Department,G to Ka, 1870s-1950 (Box 309)
    - Out of service storehouse department employees - Cloo to F, 1870s-1950 (Box 310)
    - Out of service engineering department 10 employees - saake to zwo, 1870s-1950 (Box 311a)
    - Out of service car department 40 employees - abar to bizz, 1870s-1950 (Box 311b)
    - Out of service employees Locomotive Department prior to 1959 Wim to Zzif and out of service engine department prior to 1950 Aar-Brk, 1870s-1950 (Box 312a)
    - Out of service employees engine department prior to 1950 Bro - Dj, 1870s-1950 (Box 312b)
    - Locomotive Department out of service employees prior to 1950, Cop to Goz, 1870s-1950 (Box 313a-313b)
    - Locomotive Department out of service employees prior to 1950, Kr to Myz, 1870s-1950 (Box 314a-314b)
    - Engine Department out of service employees prior to 1950, Dobb to Harr, 1870s-1950 (Box 315a)
    - Engine Department out of service employees prior to 1950, Has to L'Henseux, 1870s-1950 (Box 315b)
    - Stores Department out of service employees prior to 1950, Millert to P, 1870s-1950 (Box 316a)
    - Stores Department out of service employees prior to 1950, Stol to Z, 1870s-1950 (Box 316b)
    - Stores Department out of service employees prior to 1950, Q to STOR, 1870s-1950 (Box 317)
    - Transportation Department out of service employees prior to 1950, Lo to McCu, 1870s-1950 (Box 318a-318b)
    - Transportation Department 50-80-20 out of service employees prior to 1950, De to Gb, 1870s-1950 (Box 319a-319b)
    - Locomotive Department out of service employees prior to 1950, Naa to Pyl, 1870s-1950 (Box 320a)
    - Locomotive Department out of service employees prior to 1950, Qou to Sfer, 1870s-1950 (Box 320b)
    - Locomotive Department out of service employees prior to 1950, Sha to Whit, 1870s-1950 (Box 321a-321b)
    - Engine Department out of service employees prior to 1950, Lib to Ryn, 1870s-1950 (Box 322a-322b)
    - Locomotive department out of service employees prior to 1950 Aa-Bozz, 1870s-1950 (Box 323a)
    - Locomotive department out of service employees prior to 1950 Bra-Coo, 1870s-1950 (Box 323b)
    - Transportation department out of service employees prior to 1950 Sp-Tra, 1870s-1950 (Box 324a)
    - Transportation department out of service employees prior to 1950 Trac-Why, 1870s-1950 (Box 324b)
    - Employee Personal Records Vensel-Wehrer, 1927-1964 (Box 325)
    - Locomotives Dept. out of service employees prior to 1950; GR to KOZ, 1870s-1950 (Box 327a-327b)
    - Locomotives Dept. out of service employee records, 1870s-1950 (Box 328a-328c)
    - Employee records, 1870s-1950 (Box 331a-332c)
    - NYC system instructions for operation of diesel-electric locomotives; files pertaining to ads on cars, station record of movements, wreck trucks; Newell accident report; card file of widows, pensioners, deceased, 1952-1988 (Box 333)
    - Employee files A through D; register of Lake Shore & Michigan Southern Railway Co. employees, 1900-1980 (Box 335a)
    - Employee files E through J and R, 1900-1980 (Box 335b)
    - Employee files S through Z, 1900-1980 (Box 335c)
    - Employee out of service record cards (trainmen, engineers, clerks, yardmasters, etc), 1900-1980 (Box 336a-336d)
    - Credit cards of vehicles assigned to equipment dept.; firemen's, engineer's, and clerk's agreements; Railroad Yardmasters of America and American Train Dispatchers agreements; Transportation-Communication Employees Union; general notices; 'pink sheets', 1956-1988 (Box 369)
    - Reports of coal reserves, recoverable coal at mines, freight survey (1931-34); Ashtabula and Shenango trackage rights agreements, contracts, and reports (1976-84); Union mediation agreements (90s), 1931-44; 1976-91 (Box 370)
    - Records of employees from P&LE at Montour, 1950-1981 (Box 396)
    - Paperwork and correspondence between the railroad and various labor unions (Sheet Metal Workers, International Association of Machinists, etc.); employee vacation agreements, time lost, furlough, 1969-1990 (Box 415a)
    - Paperwork and correspondence between railroad and various labor unions, including strikes; disposal of hazardous waste and refuse; scrapped cars; office supply orders; news releases and articles concerning labor issues, accidents, and other company issues, 1969-1990 (Box 415b)
    - Company vehicles and insurance of, freight maintenance, employee training, accounting, employee bulletin, 1970-1980 (Box 420)
    - General notices; car men's agreements; 1967 Strike time claims; jurisdiction disputes; conference and grievances of Transport Workers Union of America, 1944-1972 (Box 435)
    - Water pipelines and construction blueprints; worker payrolls and estimates of expenses, 1914-1946 (Box 439)
    - Mechanical department employee rosters, 1980-1988 (Box 446)
    - Various publications on industry research; publications from conference proceedings and workshops; P&LE employee handbook; Carnegie Steel publication on "rails and angle bars;" worker safety pamphlets, 1920-1982 (Box 451)
    - Car department holidays and jury duties; matters of National Railroad Adjustment Board; complaints of cabooses; Working Agreements with C.I.O., 1934-1979 (Box 452)
    - Daily Coal Sheets; trainmen's weekly vacation assignments; clerical advertisements; railroad agreement on standards; contractor card index, 1900-1988 (Box 456)
    - L.E.S.A.D.F.employee records cards (1860-1920), rates of pay agreements (1972-73); insurance and decrease of forced furloughed employees and employees recalled; monthly report of employee movements; car dept. and painters and carpenters twice a month report; TWU of A new employees and out of service, 1860-1980 (Box 460-461)
    - Employee records cards; occupation description and pay; office of freight car utilization agent's of P&LE business and activities; management positions; performance; middle management; clerks; vacations, 1967-1982 (Box 462)
    - Employees paid to attend court; public relations instruction; USDT ads for cars and dynamite; 14th annual RR conference; GE employee education; operations stats; Pittsburgh Chamber of Commerce Meeting minutes; Brotherhood of Railroad (1990); signed worker agreements; teamsters; labor relations, 1971-1990 (Box 463)
    - Union agreements (International Brotherhood of Firemen and Oiler, Sheet metal Workers International, International Association of Machinists, Electrical Workers, International Brotherhood of Boilermakers); grievances, 1970s (Box 465)
    - TWU Agreements and working agreements; Machinery & Airbrakes exam series; 1990 Joint Inspection--B&LE and P seniority rosters; mechanical dept. locomotives, College, PA (1981); engineering mileage chart logs, 1967-1990 (Box 469)
    - Labor agreements, working agreements, cases of investigation with TWU; agreements with CIO & TWU, 1969-1975 (Box 470)
    - Various records of employee matters including: seniority district records of employment, advertisements, and awards; resumes; clerks in military service (40s); suspensions; leave of absence, 1948-1988 (Box 471)
    - Correspondence regarding employee orientation programs; college graduate training programs and courses; strikes; P&LE anniversaries and other employee events; safety equipment and programs; holidays and vacations; labor agreements; labor organizations, 1950-1992 (Box 473)
    - Medical forms; employment rates; applications; employment status updates; discipline reports; retirement, 1980s (Box 474)
    - Applications for employment; agreement for machinists, sheet metal and electrical workers, and blacksmiths; employee job protection; affirmative action compliance program monthly report to personnel department, 1966-1990 (Box 475)
    - Locomotive and Car Department accident and personal injury reports, 1957-1960 (Box 477)
    - Wheeling-Pittsburgh Steel Corporation hot slab movement; postage meter machine bills; supplementary pension-funded contributory retirement plan; allowances account for sick or dead employees; hot metal movements (McKeesport, Neville Island, etc), 1936-1985 (Box 479)
    - Transport Workers Union of American claims, 1965-1968 (Box 481)
    - Correspondence concerning Wheeling-Pittsburgh Steel rail rolling mill - Monessen, PA; pension agreement; International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers; personal injury payments; Employee Protective Fund; bargaining proposals to non-operating unions, 1966-1992 (Box 490)
    - Claims awaiting appeal; files of various railroad and transportation organizations; organization claims; district group advertisements and awards; vacation agreements for mechanical dept. and Maintenance of Way, 1980s (Box 492)
    - Equal opportunity; labor allowances; employee files, Union Agreements and correspondence, 1986-1992 (Box 495)
    - Transport Workers Union of American claims case files, 1958-1961 (Box 497)
    - Car and Engineering dept cards of employees out of service prior to 1950, 1880s-1950 (Box 498)
    - Personal injury and relative insurance paperwork, Association of American Railroads efficiency research program, AAR manual of standards and records practices, vendor offers, 1972-1984 (Box 499)
    - Employees and seniority rosters 1931, 1937, 1940, 1943, 1982-1987, 1931-1987 (Box 500)
    - Legal notes to CSX regarding agreements with ARASA; pay; health services; 1990 review of labor and union agreements, 1990-1992 (Box 501)
    - Personnel records dealing with retirement & out of service; employee card index (1880s-1950) deceased, furloughed, etc., 1880s-1982 (Box 502)
    - Director of Labor Relations and Personnel, employee time claims and grievances, 1959-1960 (Box 504)
    - Employee personnel records, 1970s (Box 507)
    - Time claims and grievances (P&LE vs. various unions), 1959-1965 (Box 508)
    - Car department out of service employee cards Slaab - Zrytka, 1903-1940 (Box 509)
    - Time claims and grievances (P&LE vs. various unions), 1950-1970 (Box 510-511)
    - Injury and illness reports and statements (1977-92); authorized positions (1984-86); freight car repairs and mechanical department requests for appropriation (1986-89); sale of cars to Chessie system (1986-89); pollution notices (1981-86); Mass Transit Clean Air Act (1974); caboose safety complaints (1968-85); power plants (1963-79); electricity (1968-86); AAR committees, correspondence and reports (1979-91); employee travel and business expenses (1985-92); utility contracts and agreements, 1963-1991 (Box 512)
    - Out of service employee cards AC-ZY, 1910-1950 (Box 538)
    - Operations; seniority rosters; department agreements; employment, 1979-1988 (Box 542b)
    - Various departmental agreements; employee pensions retirement, and hiring; interchange agreements and car reports, 1982-1988 (Box 543a)
    - Human resources; payroll; instructions to yard masters and clerks; office equipment, 1982-1988 (Box 543b)
    - Human resources, trainmen agreements, interchange agreements and instructions, movement of cars, tender notices, 1970-1979 (Box 546a)
    - Time claims, "safety first" correspondence; personal injury; car accidents; general notices and bulletins; bills; cost operations, 1973-1979 (Box 547a)
    - Car file individual updates; bundles of daily report of employees working punitive times, 1986-1988 (Box 557)
    - Monthly safety meeting; accident reports, lost time, handwritten call directory file book (R.I.Z.), benefits, monthly time book ledger, 1957-1990 (Box 559)
    - Employee record cards including disciplinary action, carols, furloughs, returns, Ba-Mc, 1880-1960s (Box 561)
    - Employee record cards including disciplinary action, carols, furloughs, returns, Na - Var, 1880-1960s (Box 562)
    - Out of service employee record cards including disciplinary action, carols, furloughs, returns, A - Wo, 1880-1960s (Box 563)
    - Index of out of service employees from all divisions (track, bridges, buildings, signal, and communications), 1900-1990 (File-cabinet 582)
    - Index of out of service, retired employees from all divisions (track, bridges, buildings, signal, and communications), 1900-1990 (File-cabinet 583)
    - Index of working & furloughed employees from all divisions (track, bridges, buildings, signal, and communications); small binders of employee addresses and emergency data, 1900-1990 (File-cabinet 584)
    - Index of deceased employees from all divisions (track, bridges, buildings, signal, and communications), 1900-1990 (File-cabinet 585)
    - Employee (Crew) Records, 2-20, 24-28, 54-72, 1873-1961 (Box 620-626)
    - Employee (Crew) Records, 73-74 [1905-1940]; Record of Telegraphers [1882-1924]; P&LE Division Records Books [1926-1927], 1882-1940 (Box 627)
    - Engineers Record Book [1936-1961]; Index to Suspended Discipline Record [1957-1962]; Foreign Record Book [1955-1965], 1936-1965 (Box 628)
    - B&O Employee Records Book [1934-1961]; Employee (Crew) Records [1883-1916]; Employee (telephone and telegraph operators) Records [1910-1919], 1883-1961 (Box 629)
    - Engineers and Firemen, Books 29, 30, 33 [1938-1961]; Clerks, Book 31 [1941-1959]; Trainmen, Book 32 [1941-1961]; Firemen, Book 34 [1944-1961] (Box 630)
    - Clerks and Operators, Book 35 [1943-1960]; Rejections, Book 36 [1947-1960]; Employee (Crew) Record Books, Books 51-53 [1900-1936], 1900-1960 (Box 631)
  - Legal, 1850-1994; 5.
    Legal records appear in this collection in the form of leases with other railroads, companies, or banks; claims and grievances made by employees, other companies, or the public; related litigation; and government regulatory documents, such as by the Interstate Commerce Commission.
    - Annual Reports to the Interstate Commerce Commission, 1964-1984 (Box 4)
    - Legal documents (land transfers, etc); Office of Engineer building specs for various equipment and implementation (ex. switches), 1915-1946 (Box 8)
    - Cases-United Railroad Workers of America M-1 to M-245, 1950-1959 (Box 16)
    - Documents delivered to Justice Department, Iron Ore/Great Lakes Antitrust Case, 1985 (Box 37)
    - Documents, Anti-Trust files, 1980s (Box 38)
    - Financial Standing 1977 Report, calendar andplanners, 1970s (Box 39)
    - Regional Rail Reorganization Act Files, 1970s (Box 40)
    - B&O Trackage Agreement, Maps, 1982 (Box 41)
    - Dart Trucking v. Baltimore & Ohio RR, Discovery (P&LE documents selected by Plaintiff), 1982 (Box 42)
    - Pinney Dock v. Penn Central, 1989 (Box 43)
    - P. 7 Flagging Case - Rule 99, 1982 (Box 44)
    - Crowell/ Bristol Litigation, 1982 (Box 45)
    - Miscellaneous Ex Parte Proceedings, 1982 (Box 46)
    - 1978 BRAC Strike, 1982 (Box 47)
    - Law Dept case files, 1980s (Box 48)
    - Crowell/ Bristol Litigation, 1982 (Box 49)
    - Crowell/ Bristol Litigation, 1982 (Box 51)
    - Ex Parte 252 law file, 1982 (Box 50)
    - Willis Trucking v. Balt. & Ohio RR, et al., 1957 (Box 57)
    - Ex Parte 334, 1982 (Box 58)
    - P&LE/LKS Coal Files; leases; case files, 1970s-1980s (Box 59)
    - Case files; Law 375-C to 379-1, 1969-1988 (Box 60)
    - Documents Furnished PCTC Trustees RE: Sale of P&LE (April 1977) (Box 61)
    - P&LE/LKS Coal Files, 1982 (Box 62)
    - Documents Filed by R. L. Banks & Associates with U.S. Department of Justice in Response to Order of Special Court, 1977 (Box 63)
    - P&LE/LKS Coal Files, 1982 (Box 64)
    - Pinney Dock v. Penn Central, et al. No. C80-1733, U.S.D.C., N.D., Ohio, 1989 (Box 65)
    - Case files, 1980s (Box 66)
    - Penn Central Merger F.D. 21989-90, Recording of interview of attorney Brandon By Jim Westover on Program "PM" radio station KDKA, 1974 (Box 67)
    - F.D. 29430 - Norfolk Western/ Southern, trackage rights, 1981 (Box 68)
    - Ex Parte Proceedings, Investigation of Railroad Freight Rate, 1982 (Box 69)
    - Ex Parte 241, Investigation of Adequacy of Railroad Freight Car Ownership, 1982 (Box 72)
    - Potomac Electric Power v, Baltimore & Ohio Railroad, Comm. F.D. 37872, 1983 (Box 71)
    - Reports before the Interstate Commerce Commission (1928, 1927, 1967), Supreme Court Regional Rail Reorganization Act Cases, Agreement for Railroad consolidation (1914), Circuit Court Case Lemley v. Morgantown and Wheeling Railway Co (1920), Various Papers/ newspaper clippings, Booklet of Miscellaneous trivia from Chicago papers about excursion fares, 3 centavo Stamp from Nicaragua (1911 mint condition), 1921-1949 (Box 85)
    - Fields v. P&LE, minority stockholder litigation, 1979 (Box 106)
    - Investigation of adequacy of railroad freight car ownership, car utilization, distribution, rules and practices, 1979 (Box 107)
    - Passenger train abandonment of services - discontinuance, 1960s (Box 108)
    - Duane Koontz v. P&LE, Pierce v. P&LE, Miller v. P&LE, Farone v. P&LE, West v. P&LE, Graham v. P&LE, Sekelik v. P&LE, Ledford v. P&LE, Hines v. P&LE, 1980s (Box 109)
    - Delaware and Hudson Railway Bankruptcy, CSX vs. Monongahela Railroad, Burlington Northern Railroad Co. vs. P&LE, Norfolk Western vs. P&LE, 1970s-1980s (Box 110)
    - Files for Grand Jury Subpoena of October 27, 1980, has a file log (Box 111)
    - Pinney Dock vs. Penn Central, 1980s (Box 112)
    - Baltimore and Ohio Statements, B & O Interstate Commerce Commission reports with P&LE, 1960s (Box 113)
    - Files for Grand Jury Subpoena of Oct 27, 1980 (Box 114)
    - Crowell/ Bristol Litigation, 1980 (Box 115)
    - B&O/C&O Control, 1980 (Box 116)
    - Pinney Dock vs. Penn Central, 1980 (Box 117)
    - ICC Proceedings - Penn Central Bankruptcy (1973) (Box 118)
    - EEOC Matters, facilities information etc., 1973 (Box 119)
    - Case files: 299-326 a (George Vennebush v. P&LE), 299-362 (Lafrankie v. P&LE), 299-378 (Wagner v. P&LE), 299-391 (Coates v. P&LE and City of Pittsburgh), 299-392 a (Coates v. P&LE and City of Pittsburgh), 299-394 (Blumling v. P&LE, Monal Construction, Jones-Krall, and C.A. Muer Corp), 299-395 (Schrey v. P&LE), 1980s (Box 120)
    - Martin Marietta Aluminum Inc. v AT&SF, Kaiser Aluminum & Chemical, 1980s (Box 121)
    - Case files: 299-126 (Becker v. P&LE), 299-140 (Mannas v. P&LE), 299-137 (Brandstadter v. P&LE), 299-131 (Fisher v. P&LE), 299-151 (Vennebush v. P&LE), 299-151 a (Vennebush v. P&LE), 299-216 (Slonchka v. P&LE), 299-167 ( Holfelder Jr. v. P&LE), 299-179 (Rosko v. P&LE), 299-187 (Smetanka v. Vesche and P&LE, 299-188 (Bacha v. P&LE), 299-189 (Zollinger v. P&LE), 299-292 (Zitcovich v. P&LE), 299-195 (Malloy v. P&LE), 299-199 (McCabe v. P&LE), 299-202 (Buerkle v. P&LE), 299-205 ( Grumbling v. P&LE), 1970s (Box 122)
    - Pinney Dock Litigation (Republic Steel, Tauro, HG Allyn- Unkovic files), 1989 (Box 123)
    - Documents delivered to Justice Department, Iron Ore/ Great Lakes Antitrust Case, 1980 (Box 124)
    - 299-387 ( Yohman v. P&LE), 299-415 (Donofrio v. P&LE), 299-429 (Bethune v. P&LE), 299-498 (Bethune v. P&LE), 299-435 (Winston v. P&LE), 299-446 ( Sovern v. P&LE), 299-448 ( Feinaugle v. P&LE), 299-452 ( Iudiciani v. P&LE), 299-461 ( Davis v. P&LE), 1980s (Box 125)
    - Stagers Acts, Section 229 Complaints, 1985 (Box 126)
    - Montour Land Co. File 182, Delinquent Accounts File 190, Library File 381, Workmen's Compensation File 592, Pittsburgh History and Landmarks Foundation, 1967-1981 (Box 127)